So, a lot of times, what y'all are determining to be dictators are really just nation-state leaders with independent thought.
What I mean by that is they are not answering to another's agenda.
And I have a homeboy who always says, everybody got somebody they don't want to see.
When it comes to the concept of the dictator, what it means, particularly in the United States and Western context, is that there is nobody above that person.
Thus, they cannot control that person.
They don't have an end road to basically undermine that person's ability to run their country and control their resources.
Y'all know nothing about that.
That's when you see sanctions put in.
That's when you see coups happen.
That's when you see disabilizing happening, etc.
Because they're like, no, we...
I gotta fix that.
They're like, no, there's already folks that run the world and you need to answer to them.
And the dictators are like, nah, y'all may run the world, but you don't run me.
So, you can't just look at the idea of the dictator under one lens.
When you have people that have been in office for an extended amount of time that are supported by colonizers,
those are puppets.
When you have folks that have been in office for a long amount of time that are not supported by colonizers,
I'm not saying that they shouldn't have to answer to their constituency.
I'm not saying that they shouldn't have to answer to some elected body.
I'm absolutely saying that.
However, the nuance is important.
And for the record, a lot of the folks that you are electing, they're not leaders at all.
They're not elected so that they can lead.
They're not elected to have independent thought.
They're elected to carry out the wishes and the initiatives and the agenda of a greater power.
And for the last thing I want to say is that a lot of y'all who be like on my head, like,
you don't ever have solutions.
You have never run anything other than your mouth.
And I have been a leader my entire life.
So, if you're not hearing solutions, it's because you've got indoctrination stuck in your ear.
We're going to find the solidarity.
Listen to your people.
Because I am a billionaire.
I am a billionaire.